gotickets.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy | PRIMESPORT

## Preamble

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy“) applies to www.primesport.com (and its respective subdomains) and the various social networking platforms that we use (each, a “Site” and collectively the “Sites”). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect when using the Sites and in our providing of our Services ( we will refer to your use of the Sites and our Services collectively as the “Services”), how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.

The Site is operated by PrimeSport, LLC and its corporate affiliates (including its parent company, On Location Events, LLC) (referred to collectively in this policy as “we,” “us,” “our” and other similar pronouns). You understand and agree that any information collected via the Site (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) shall be jointly owned by us and our affiliates.

By using our Services, you acknowledge that we will use your information in the United States and any other country where we operate. Please be aware that the privacy laws and standards in certain countries, including the rights of authorities to access your personal information, may differ from those that apply in the country in which you reside. We will transfer personal information only to these countries to which we are permitted by law to transfer personal information, and we will take steps to ensure that your personal information continues to enjoy appropriate protections. As our business evolves, this Policy may change, so check back to this page periodically to make sure you understand how your personal information will be treated.

## TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED

In the course of providing our Services, we collect or receive your personal information in a few different ways. Often, you choose what information to provide, but sometimes we require certain information for you to use and for us to provide you the Services.

## Information You Provide Us

In the course of using our Services, we may ask you or require you to provide us with personally identifiable information, which is information that can be used to identify you as an individual or allow someone to contact you in providing our Services, such as:

your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or fax number

unique identifiers, such as your user ID, or user password

credit card and other payment information

demographic information

IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data

As is the case with many websites, our servers automatically collect your IP address when you visit our Site, and we may associate that with your domain name or that of your Internet access provider. We may also capture certain “clickstream data” pertaining to your Site usage. Clickstream data includes, for example, information about your computer or device, web browser and operating system and their settings, the referring page that linked you to the Site, the pages, content or ads you see or click on during your visit and when and for how long you do so, items you download, the next website you visit when you leave the Site, and any search terms you have entered on the Site or a referral site.

## Cookies

Cookies are small data files stored on your computer or device at the request of a Web site. A cookie assigns a unique numerical identifier to your Web browser, and may enable us to recognize you as the same user who was at our Site in the past, and relate your use of the Site to other information about you, such as your Site usage information and personal information. Cookies may also be used to enhance your experience on the Site (for example, by storing your username so you can log in easily, keeping you logged into the Site after you have provided your password, and storing the contents of your shopping cart as you browse) or to collect general usage and aggregated statistical information and detect and prevent fraud. Most browsers can be set to detect cookies and give you an opportunity to reject them, but refusing cookies may, in some cases, inhibit or preclude your use of the Site or its features. To learn more about the use of cookies, including how to manage or delete them, [click here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

In addition to being able to control cookies by changing the settings in your browser on your computer, or in your mobile device’s settings, you can also control which companies can set cookies and similar technologies on your devices, by visiting the following links (you’ll need to turn any cookie or ad blockers off for the control pages to show which companies you can opt-out of):

The [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) (NAI) control page allows you to control behavioral advertising from each of the ad networks represented by the NAI.

The [Digital Advertising Alliance’s](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/) self-regulatory program for online behavioral advertising control page allows you to control behavioral advertising from the ad networks it represents.

Importantly, these ad networks set cookies to remember that you have chosen to opt-out. If you clear your cache the opt-outs will not be applied and you would need to opt-out again.

## Flash LSOs

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies [click here](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html).

## Web Beacons and Other Tracking Technology

The Site uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of web sites. We also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on the Site, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of the Site. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send to determine whether the recipients have opened those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable.

## HTML5

HTML5 (the language some web sites are coded in) may be used to store information on your computer or device about your Site usage activities. This information can be retrieved by us to determine how our Site is being used by our visitors, how it can be improved, and to customize it for our users.

These tracking technologies may be deployed by us and/or by our service providers or partners on our behalf. These technologies enable us to assign a unique number to you, and relate your Site usage information to other information about you, including your personal information. These technologies also enable us to recognize you when you access our Site using different Web browsers and different computers or devices.

## Email Communications 

When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation notifying us that you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have selected to receive or not to receive. If you would like to opt-out of receiving such emails, please click on the “unsubscribe” link in the email and follow the instructions.

## Information from Other Sources

We may receive information about you (e.g., missing street number) from other sources and add it to your personal information.

## Who We May Share Your Data With

We may share your personal information with third parties. The parties we may share your information with include:

Our Service Providers: We employ other business service providers and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf for various purposes including email services, web analytics, marketing, and customer service. They may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but are restricted from using or disclosing it for other purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.

Affiliates: We may share your information (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) with all members of our corporate family, including, without limitation, our subsidiaries and affiliates.

Third Party Partners: We may share your information with third party(s) (including the NFL and all other game/event organizers and participating schools/teams) for third party marketing purposes so that they may send you information or direct marketing offers, unless you tell us not to by following the instructions in the Opt-in and Opt-out section above.

Contest Co-Sponsors: We may share your information with our co-sponsor(s) if we obtain your information in connection with a contest, sweepstakes, offering, or other promotional activity that is jointly offered by us and any third parties, unless you instruct us not to by following the instructions in the Opt-in and Opt-out section above.

Third Party Ad Servers and Networks. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site or to serve our ads on third-party Web sites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites, the region of the country or world where your IP address indicates you are located, as well as other information about you in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These advertisements may appear on this Site and on other Web sites. These companies may employ cookies, clear GIFs and other tracking technologies to cause relevant ads to be displayed to you. We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies to learn about how they treat your information.

Business Transfers: In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred, all personally identifiable information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer. You will be notified of such a transfer in accordance with the “Changes to the Policy” section below.

Administrative or Legal Process: We or others may disclose your personal information to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law, law enforcement agencies, to protect our or third parties’ rights, or to protect the rights of other users of the Site.

## YOUR ACCESS AND CHOICES

## OPT IN AND OPT OUT

You may have the right to opt in to or opt out of certain of our uses and disclosures of your personal information. For example, when you are asked to provide personal information on this Site, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to, receive messages from us by e-mail or, if applicable, text messages. You may tell us that you do not want to receive our promotional messages, or that you do not want us to share your personal information with third parties for their marketing purposes by sending us your name, address, e-mail and phone number to:

PrimeSport, LLC, 3575 Piedmont Rd., Bldg 15 - Suite 950, Atlanta, Georgia, 30305, ATTN: Privacy Administrator

Email: privacypolicy@primesport.com

You can opt out from your data being used by Google Analytics by visiting https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout .

You can also opt-out of our promotional emails by clicking on the opt-out link within the e-mail you receive.

To opt out of our text messages, please follow the opt-out instructions in the terms and conditions for the text messaging program that you signed up for.

Please indicate whether you are asking us to stop sharing your information with third parties, or if you are writing to request that you no longer receive a particular media notification from us. Please understand that it may take us a few days to process any opt out request and that even if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us. Also, to stop receiving promotional messages from third parties who already have your contact information, please contact them directly.

## Your choice to receive personalized advertisements

Advertisements displayed to you on this Site and elsewhere may be customized to your interests and preferences based on your personally identifiable information and usage information collected through our Site unless you opt out by following the instructions that can be found at the Digital Advertising Alliance’s consumer choice site http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or the Network Advertising Initiative’s consumer choice site at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ You have to opt-out using each of your Web browsing applications and devices separately. However, if you opt-out we may still suggest offerings to you on our Site based on your history at our Site.

## HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

We (jointly with the NFL Entities) own the information collected on or through the Site. As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used by us or our service providers to:

contact you about the Site;

provide you with services or information you have requested or products or services you have registered for or other products and services;

contact you regarding a specific product of interest;

contact you regarding future product offerings;

monitor or improve the use of the Site;

market research;

monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Site;

process and fulfill your transactions;

send you promotional material or special offers of ours, or on behalf of any NFL Entities, our other marketing partners, licensed sales agents and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Opt In and Opt Out section above;

protecting our rights and property;

recovering debt and preventing fraud;

customizing our Site to your interests and history with us;

tailoring ads displayed to you on our Site and elsewhere to your interests and history with us; and

other purposes disclosed when personal information is submitted to us.

To perform the above functions, we may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both personal information and Site usage information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources (including third parties) such as demographic information and updated contact information. We or our service providers may also use your information to assess the level of interest in, and use of, the Site, our e-mails and our other messaging campaigns both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

## SOCIAL NETWORKING

We maintain presence on several social networking and blogging platforms, such as Facebook and Twitter, and we also incorporate some third party social networking features onto our Site. Through these platforms and features, we receive some personal information and some Site usage information about you, and this Privacy Policy applies to that information as well. We may also include tools on our Site that allow you to share and/or publicly post content or information from our Site to your profile on a third party social network. Third party social networking platforms and blogging platforms have their own privacy policies which explain how they will use, protect and share your information, including any information you share on those platforms from our Site, and we encourage you to read them.

## DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURES

Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” (DNT) signals to the websites with which the user communicates. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. We currently do not change our tracking practices (which are explained in more detail above) in response to DNT settings in your web browser.

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

You should be aware that when you are on the Site you could be directed to other websites beyond our control. For example, if you “click” on a banner advertisement, the “click” may take you off the Site onto a different website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Site’s logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to the Site, you should consult that website’s privacy policy before providing any personal information.

## SECURITY

While we endeavor to protect the security and integrity of sensitive Personal Information collected via this Site, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that any information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

If you correspond with us by e-mail, text message, or using web forms like a “Contact Us” feature on our Site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view the information you send in transit by such means. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

If you create an account on our Site, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any activity that occurs using your account credentials, whether or not you authorized such activity. Please notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security.

If we believe that the security of any user’s personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify such user of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as the means of such notification. However, if you do not want to be notified by email for this purpose, please contact us at privacypolicy@primesport.com.

## CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS, AND MESSAGE BOARDS

The Site may make chat rooms, forums, commenting and message boards available to you and other users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. By using the commenting features of the Site, you acknowledge that your user name and location information will be disclosed. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacypolicy@primesport.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY

The Site is a general audience website. On the Site, we do not currently knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association’s website (http://www.the-dma.org) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise website (http://www.getnetwise.org) to learn more about parental control tools.

## CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Policy from time to time. When we do, we will let you know by posting the changed Policy on this page with a new “Last Updated” date. In some cases (for example, if we significantly expand our use or sharing of your Personal Information), we may also tell you about changes by additional means, such as by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address we have on file for you. In some cases, we may request your consent to the changes.

## CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address or zip code), or if you no longer desire to have access to the Site, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us. You may request that we do so by emailing us at privacypolicy@primesport.com and requesting that the desired changes be made, or via mail at: PrimeSport, LLC, 3575 Piedmont Rd., Bldg 15 - Suite 950, Atlanta, Georgia, 30305, ATTN: Privacy Administrator. We may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information. Your right to delete your information is subject to our records retention policies.

## COPY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may request a copy of your personal information from us and you can also ask us to correct any inaccuracies in your personal information. You may also have the right to object, erase, or restrict our processing of your information. To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at privacypolicy@primesport.com. If you make any of the above requests, we will do this as soon as is reasonably possible under the circumstances of the request(s).

## RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will retain your information for as long as necessary for the uses set out in this Policy, or while there is a legitimate reason for doing so. If you ask us to delete your information before that time, we may not be able to do so due to technical, legal, regulatory or contractual constraints. For example, we would need to retain your name and contact details for suppression purposes if you do not want to receive direct marketing from us.

## YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to privacypolicy@primesport.com or write us at PrimeSport, LLC, 3575 Piedmont Rd., Bldg 15 - Suite 950, Atlanta, Georgia, 30305, ATTN: Privacy Administrator

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, contact privacypolicy@primesport.com.

## USERS FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION

This section of the Privacy Policy applies only if you use our Services covered by this Privacy Policy from a country that is a Member State of the European Union, and supplements the information in this Privacy Policy.

On Location Events, LLC is the data controller for processing of information defined as personal data under applicable data protection law ("Personal Data").

Legal Basis for Data Processing: We process Personal Data for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, as described above. Our legal basis to process personal data includes processing that is: necessary for the performance of any contract between you and us (for example, to provide you with the Services you request and to identify and authenticate you so you may use the website); necessary to comply with legal requirements (for example, to comply with applicable accounting rules and to make mandatory disclosures to law enforcement); necessary for our legitimate interests (for example, to manage our relationship with you and to improve the Site and our Services); and based on consent by our customers (for example, to communicate with you about our products and services and provide you with marketing information), which may subsequently be withdrawn at any time (by emailing privacypolicy@primesport.com) without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. In some instances, you may be required to provide us with Personal Data for processing as described above, in order for us to be able to provide you all of our Services, and for you to use all the features of our website. You may lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your Personal Data infringes applicable law.

Copy of Personal Information: You may request a copy of your personal information from us and you can also ask us to correct any inaccuracies in your personal information. You may also have the right to object, erase, or restrict our processing of your information. To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at privacypolicy@primesport.com. If you make any of the above requests, we will do this as soon as is reasonably possible under the circumstances of the request(s).

## QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of this Site, please contact us by email at privacypolicy@primesport.com or: PrimeSport, LLC, 3575 Piedmont Rd., Bldg 15 - Suite 950, Atlanta, Georgia, 30305, ATTN: Privacy Administrator
